kara.com.ng 2017-12-18

# Privacy Policy

We value our customers and visitors to our site at kara.com.ng. Hence we insist on the highest standards for all transactions customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To ensure you have updated information, it is advised that you visit this section periodically.

**1\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number and addresses) from you when you set up an account with kara.com.ng. While you can browse some sections of our site without being a registered member, certain activities (such as placing an order) do require registration.  We use your contact information to send you invoices, offers and conversion notices based on your orders and your interests.

**2\. Use of Demographic and Profile Data**

We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. We use your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; collect fees owed; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.  In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our website. 

**Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. kara.com.ng's cookies do not contain any of your personal identifiable information.

**3\. Sharing of personal information**

We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to: help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.

kara.com.ng and its affiliates will share some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a transaction occur that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.

**4\. Links to Other Sites**

Our site may link to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Kara.com.ng is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.

**5\. Security Precautions**

Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

**6\. Choice/Opt-Out**

kara.com.ng provides all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account.  If you want to remove your contact information from all kara.com.ng lists and newsletters, please visit http://www.kara.com.ng/unsubscribe.php

**7\. Advertisements on Kara.com.ng**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**8\. Questions?**

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the following address: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#1566747970664a7e74677455677a6c7479767a7466613872677a60653b767a78)

**ADDENDUM**

As you browse kara.com.ng, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.  Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with kara.com.ng. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.  You can visit this [page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.
